CIRCUIT ANGEL
~Ketsui no Starting Grid~
Tenohira atsuku sora ni kazashi
Đưa tay lên để che mắt khỏi cái nắng của bầu trời.
Yubi no saki made kanjitaiyo
Em muốn cảm nhận cái nắng
trên đầu ngón tay của mình.
Ima wa toki o kurikaerazu
Hiện giờ thì thời gian đã
không thể quay lại được nữa.
Hashitteyukeru to, do you know?
Em có thể chạy mất đấy, anh biết không?
Otona no furi wa atomawashisa
Việc ra vẻ người lớn có thể để sau.
Kokoro no mama ni sakebitaiyo
Em muốn hét lên từ sâu thẳm trong tim mình.
Daijina no wa jibun jishin
Thứ quan trọng nhất chính là bản thân chúng ta.
Shinjiteitai to, do you know?
Em muốn có thể tin vào điều đó, anh biết không?
Mari's got a 250?
We're going to have fun next time we go touring!
Her dad's pretty lenient.
Well, that's...
Here you go.
Thanks.
What were you saying?
She got it on condition that she helps her father carrying out deliveries.
Delivering sushi with a 250??
Looks like all that nigiri is gonna be ruined!
It's just going to turn into chirashi in the end.
You said it.
Oh man, what a mess.
You idiot!
I already said I'm sorry!
You can't get away with this just with an apology!
Driving around like crazy while carrying goods...
I don't remember raising my daughter like this!
Look who's talking!
What kind of father attacks his own daughter?
Shut up! I ought to spank your ass!
My ass?
Dad, you're too vulgar.
Shut up!
As your punishment, I'm going to keep the key to your bike!
Good grief, how did you grow up to be so ill-mannered?
Sorry about that.
Seriously, what does he expect from me?
Eh?
Goodnight...
I don't want to go alone...
But... My dad won't listen to anything I say.
I'll ask again once he's in a better mood.
It'll take at least a week.
How about you just go without permission?
No way.
Why?
I hate doing things like that.
Hardhead.
Sorry.
I just don't like acting sneaky.
Mariko!
Is it true you can't go touring with us?
Keiichi...
Despite saying all that, I've still got to do this...
Mariko!
What do you think you're doing?
You're going way too fast,
especially for a beginner!
I'm doing fine.
Idiot! If something happens to you,
your dad's gonna chew us out!
Why do you think you're responsible for me?
Huh? Isn't it obvious?
What are you doing?
You're not a very popular guy, are you?
You're more annoying than helpful!
Mariko! That's enough already! Listen to me!
Can't hear you!
Huh, that guy isn't half bad.
That's not a guy.
Welcome.
Have you seen Mariko?
No.
Thought so. That punk!
Mister!
Well, you see...
Even I know bikes aren't that dangerous
as long as you follow the regulations.
But...
I don't like the way she acts!
Cut her some slack.
People tend to act reckless when they're young.
That includes doing things
behind their parent's backs.
Don't you remember being like that once too?
Even I've done things I regret now
without even realizing it...
Being worried is part of a parent's job, huh...
Isn't anyone following me?
Is that Keiichi?
Doesn't look like him.
I won't let you get past!
He's good!
Don't stick too close or you'll regret it!
Unbelievable...
Awesome!
Hey Hiroko, have you grown bigger again?
That's right!
Looks like I'll have to get a new bra soon.
What do you eat to get that big?
It's not about what you eat, dummy!
Hey, what do you think about Keiichi?
Keiichi? He's just an old friend.
He's not the kind of guy I'd want as a boyfriend.
What kind of guys do you like then?
Me? I like...
No!
Hey Kei, we shouldn't be doing this.
Idiot! A chance like this doesn't come often!
Hiroko's going to break up with me.
A temporary breakup or nude girls,
which do you care about more?
N-nude girls!
Thought you'd say so.
Who are you people?
Who rode the bike with this thing on it?
That's mine!
I see. Only Sho can notice these kind of things.
Hey hey! You guys!
Blatantly peeking on girls is dirty!
Isn't that better than doing it sneakily?
Who's sneaking?
That's right! That's right!
People who peek on others are the worst!
Did something happen at the spring?
Give my amulet back!
Just wait! I'll definitely get it back for you!
Kei, wait! Me too!
Good timing from those two...
They were watching!!
It's too early for a break!
Step it up, kid!
Damn!
Kei, these guys are pretty tough!
Yeah, but I won't lose!
No way.
Keiichi, are you alright?
Yeah, I think so.
Hmph, you've got some skills.
What are you up to?
Nothing much. Just wanted to see you.
Well, are you happy now? Give it back.
Here ya go.
Looks like a marriage amulet.
I'll hold onto this until we meet again.
Nabeshima
Sho!
Come here for a bit.
If this is about helping you make more money, I'll pass.
Big words from a guy who likes to play around with said money.
That's the only thing that connects us as father and son, right?
What a witty retort.
More importantly,
you're entering the next race, right?
Even if I refused,
wouldn't you just force me to enter?
Obviously.
You're driving our latest model.
It'd be a shame if you didn't win.
A victory for me will raise
our popularity in an instant.
No matter how good it is, the machine won't win the race.
I will.
1969.
17 years old, huh.
Mariko Okazaki.
Your dad's pissed, right?
Well. he took away the key as usual,
but he was grateful to you!
Looks like I've gained some respect from him somehow.
He actually was wondering if he
should ask you to become his son-in-law.
I'll go change the water!
Oh, sorry -
It's you!
What are you doing here?!
A cheque?
Three million?!
It's my get-well present.
Chump change for my father.
Take it.
Stop joking around!
You can't just settle this with money!
Instead of money, just give back Mariko's amulet.
I refuse.
You...!
Enough already.
Let's not forget basic manners here.
You...
And secondly, this amount of money...
Nabeshima Mitsugu...
Mariko... I see.
You knew Nagase.
It's no wonder then.
Master!
How unusual!
Yeah. What's this?
Ah, that's a model
that was discontinued 7 years ago.
The one from that incident, remember?
The controversy is starting to wear off, though.
They're going to start producing them again.
The one who caused
the accident was Nagase, right?
That's right, Raita Nagase.
Once known as the genius "Bullet Rider".
Yeah... "Bullet Rider" Nagase.
Well, thanks to that accident
we found out what was wrong with the bike.
What?
You mean it wasn't the driver's fault?
Whoops, I didn't mean to say that!
Just forget about it, okay?
Hey!
So it wasn't a mistake on the driver's part...
Shirou sure is late...
I helped him at cleaning too.
You're almost like a dedicated wife!
Ah! A white Supra!
Yo!
You...
What do you want?
Looks like my prayers were answered.
That's my...
Give it back!
Just give it back already.
Do you want to know about Raita Nagase's past?
Raita's?
Why did he quit driving?
Quit... driving?
He got scared. Turned into a coward.
You always get on my nerves.
Raita's not that kind of person!
Don't you want to check out
whether I'm lying or not?
If you don't know the true face of Raita Nagase...
You're going to get killed by him too.
Sorry!
Shirou! Mariko got taken away by that guy!
Mari!
We gotta tell her father!
W-wait! Master...
Yeah, we should call master instead.
Yeah!
I'll go find Keiichi!
Projector Room
Number 23 is Nagase.
And here...
The man who tried to dodge Nagase
was taken to a hospital, but...
He didn't make it.
But... In that situation...
He was a good friend of Nagase's.
What's infuriating is that after the incident
Nagase never took part in a race again.
The man who lost his life by dodging him died for nothing.
He became afraid after seeing his friend die before his eyes.
Pathetic guy.
What's your point?
Quitting racing is Raita's way of taking responsibility for what happened.
Do you have any right to judge that?
I...
Mariko!! Where are you?!
Keiichi?
Let me go, you morons!
Give Mariko back!
Keiichi!
Mariko!
Mari!
You alright?
What's going on?
No need to worry!
Just try to lay a finger on her!
I'll beat you to death!
Have you fallen for her?
This idiot never ceases to amuse me.
I'll get Mariko out of here no matter what!
Calm down, Keiichi!
I'll settle this, alright?
You're first!
Ah! Master!
Nice show you've put up here.
What?!
Keiichi!
Sho! That's enough!
Dad?
Raita...
Mariko! Keiichi! What's going on?
President!
It's okay, you can go.
Yes sir!
Miss.
It seems my no-good son has been causing you trouble.
I heard from Mr. Nagase.
I apologize on his behalf.
I don't like parents who get involved in their kids fights.
The one who should be apologizing
is not you, but this person!
Sho.
I don't bow my head for people weaker than me.
So I need to get better?
I have to win against you?!
How about it. miss?
You ride bikes too, am I correct?
Let's settle this with a race.
Dad!
Mr. Nabeshima!
I've reserved Harumi Circuit for a day one month from now.
Let's have a 1 on 1 race there.
A race?
That's too much for her!
Even with the former racing legend on her side?
No, I'm...
I'll do it.
Mari! This isn't a game!
I know.
All I have to do is enter?
And win the race?
If I win...
Would that satisfy you?
What? A race, you say?
Well, I mean...
We kind of had an agreement, so...
With who?!
I didn't really ask for it!
Don't try to fool me! I won't allow this!
I definitely won't!
Well, we need to talk about that...
Hmph! What do you want?
Dad...
I need to race against him, no matter what.
"Him"?
I don't want to lose. Not to him.
He's good!
Don't stick too close or you'll regret it!
You've always told me to never run away
from a fight, ever since I was a kid!
This isn't some quarrel between kids!
That's why I want to win!
For the last time, no!!
Dad...
Mr. Okazaki...
Master, the situation being what it is...
I beg you! Please teach Mariko!
If something happened to her,
my wife would never forgive me!
Not good...
Your owner's pretty impressive.
Awesome!
A real race machine!
It's what I used to drive back in the day.
Even though it's made for racing,
it's lighter than your bikes.
Shift up and down are reversed too.
This is what I'm riding?
Nah, it's no good this way.
I'll turn it into a special bike
borrowing my friend's engineering skills.
I'll help!
Me too!
What's wrong, Keiichi?
I don't want you to do this.
Kei...
You can't do well in racing just with ordinary physical strength.
You have to do some serious training.
There's only one month. It's gonna be tough.
Yes!
What's with this covering?
Take a look at this wheel! It's all solid!
What kind of machine is this?
This is it, then?
This is the special bike, Boomerang!
I've gotten pretty muscular lately...
Would anyone want to still marry me?
Wansuke!
Well, had enough?
Mariko...
Keiichi?
Listen...
I thought I'd tell you after the race, but...
I feel like it could be too late by then.
Ever since I was a kid...
I've always loved you.
Mariko? Are you listening?
Mariko? Mariko!
Raita?
What is it?
If I win...
Will you start riding bikes again?
Mari...
Promise me, alright?
I'll think about it.
What is this bike?
Hey! What are you doing with my bike?
The bike alone won't win you the race.
It's all about your skills.
Like I wouldn't know!
If this test drive goes well,
we need to start producing those bikes again.
Yes. If it's your son,
everything should go well.
That goes without saying.
I've tolerated his stupid behavior
and always covered for him for this day's sake.
Go for it!
Do your best!
What's that?
I've never seen a bike like that before.
Did you know?
This is the bike you rode 7 years ago.
I'm not as bad as you are.
But this time the faulty parts have been fixed, Mr. Nagase.
It was defective?
How many laps are there?
Kei!
You came, Keiichi!
4 laps. Are you worried?
Obviously.
Who wouldn't be.
So fast! He's not just some spoiled brat!
Keiichi! He came after all!
Nagase built quite a bike.
His past experience as a rider sure shows.
What are you looking at?
I'm talking about the design, not the engine!
That would become a top seller for sure.
In that case, we'll start gathering information about it immediately.
I'll settle this right here!
There she is!
What's she doing?
She fell down...
Where are you going?
Isn't it obvious? To stop the race!
She can't win! It's impossible!
If you love her, then believe in her!
Boss! We found out who designed the bike!
It was Nagase's friend's company...
Boomerang?
I've caught up!
What? Impossible!
She's doing great again!
Go for it, Mariko! It's the final lap!
There's no time left!
Mom... Dad...
Watch over me!
What? She's getting too close!
Are you insane?!
She did it!! She won!!
She's definitely something...
Way to go!! Amazing!!
We only met for a moment
Deau no ga sukoshi dake
It was too late by then
Ososugita dake nanoni
Mou anata ni chikazuku no mo dekinainowa naze
Why cannot I be close to you anymore?
Hashagisugita kisetsu ga kaze no you ni sugiteku
The passing season disappeared like the wind
Chief Producer: Hiromasa Shibazaki
Ii yatsu nante dokonidemo iru nante itta mama
Even though I said good people can be found anywhere...
Screenplay: Mami Watanabe
Character Design: Chuuichi Iguchi
Special Bike Design: Boomerang
Director: Yoshikazu Tochihira
Anata ga koe wo kaketa sei yo
Because you called out to me
Mariko - Maya Okamoto
Sho - Kenyu Horiuchi
Keiichi - Keiichi Nanba
Mune ga itamu no mo, otona ni naru no mo
I felt a pain in my heart, and grew more mature
Matsutaro - Kouhei Miyauchi
Mitsugu - Ichiro Nagai
Raita - Tesshou Genda
Hiroko - Hiroko Moriguchi
Sono te wo nigirishimeta mama de
Holding your hand tightly
Saigo ni hitokoto iwasete
Let me say one last thing to you
I still love you
Deau no ga sukoshi dake
We only met for a moment
Ososugita dake nanoni
It was too late by then
Mou kono mama ano hito wo oinukenai no ne
I cannot catch up with you anymore
Tokei no hari wa itsumo wakare wo kizamu dake
The hand of the clock always seems to tick towards the time of parting
Shiawase nante dokonidemo aru nante uso nano
It's a lie that happiness can be found anywhere